L. C. Dunn Papers ca.1920-1974 Mss.B.D917
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, ca.1920-1974 (Box 1)
  - 1935-37, 20 items; Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced German Scholars (Box 9-12)
    - 45 letters, to and from, 1935-37; Whyte, John
    - 1 letter, from, August. 5, 1937; Zerner, Marianne
  - Correspondence, 1933-34; 45 items; Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced German Scholars
    - 3 letters, to and from, 1933-34; Bagster-Collins, E. W.
    - 4 letters, to and from, 1933; Boas, Franz, 1858-1942
    - 2 letters, to and from, Nov 6 and 8, 1933; Bodine, J. H.
    - 3 letters, to and from, 1933; Breit, G.
    - 1 letter, to, May 31, 1933; Bush, Vannevar, 1890-1974
    - 1 letter, from, June 8, 1933; Cattell, J. McKeen
    - 1 letter, to, June 20, 1933; Cohn, Alfred E., (Alfred Einstein), 1879-1957
    - 18 letters to and from, 1933-34; Cole, Leon J.
    - 3 letters, from, 1933; Compton, K. T., (Karl Taylor), 1887-1954
    - 1 letter, from, Feb. 12, 1934; Conant, James Bryant, 1893-1978
    - 1 letter, from, Jan. 29, 1934; Crew, F.A. E.
    - 2 letters, to and from, 1933; Davis, Watson
    - 1 letter, from, Dec. 28, 1933; Drury, Betty
    - 13 letters, to and from, 1933; Duggan, Stephen P.
    - 3 letters, to and from, 1933; Fackenthal, Frank Diehl, 1883-1968
    - 1 letter, from, July 28, 1933; Friess, Horace L.
    - 1 letter, from, May 26, 1933; Harrison, Ross G., (Ross Granville), 1870-1959
    - 3 letters, from, 1933; Hecht, Selig
    - 1 letter, from, Oct. 5, 1933; Heilbronn,(?)
    - 2 copies, to and from, 1934; LaMer, Victor K.
    - 13 letters, to and from, 1933-34; Landauer, Walter, 1896-
    - 1 letter, from, n.d; Liebowitz
    - 4 letters, to and from, 1933-34; McCracken, Charles C.
    - 28 letters, to and from, 1933-34; Murrow, Edward R.
    - 2 letters, from, 1933; Nachtsheim, Hans, 1890-1979
    - 2 copies, to and from, Paneth, F.
    - 1 letter, from, May 26, 1933; Parker, G. H.
    - 1 letter, from, May 24, 1933; Pearl, Raymond, 1879-1940
    - 1 letter, from, May 19, 1934; Pegram, George B.
    - 1 letter, from, September 12, 1933; Ritt, J. H.
    - 1 letter, from, Apr. 5, 1934; Schneider, Herbert W.
    - 1 letter, from, September 21, 1933; Staebel, (Dr.)
    - 1 letter, from, September 28, 1933; Trelease, Herbert W.
    - 1 letter, from, August. 16, 1933; Warden, C. J.
    - 4 letters, to and from, 1933; Waugh, Albert E.
    - 2 letters, to and from, Nov 17and20, 1933; Weaver, Warren
    - 3 letters, to and from, 1933; Witschi, Emil
  - 1938-39, 19 items; Emergency Committee... Columbia University
    - 1 letter, from, Dec. 5, 1938; Boas, Franz, 1858-1942
    - 2 letters, to, 1938-39; Butler, Nicholas Murray
    - 3 letters, to and from, 1938-39; Chamberlain, Joseph P.
    - 1 letter, from, Dec. 6, 1938; Clark, Hans T.
    - 1 letter, from, Dec 6, 1938; Coffin, Henry Sloane
    - 2 letters, from, Dec, 1938; Dewey, John, 1859-1952
    - 4 letter, from, 1939; Dodge, M. Hardley
    - 5 letters, to and from, 1939; Fackenthal, Frank Diehl, 1883-1968
    - 1 letter, to, May 20, 1930; Friess, Horace L.
    - 7 letters, to and from, 1938-39; Gentzler, W. Emerson
    - 1 letter from, Sept. 14, 1948; Fruton, Joseph S., (Joseph Stewart), 1912-
    - 1 letter, to, Jan. 29, 1939; Hayden, P. M.
    - 4 letters, to and from, 1938-39; Hayes, Carlton J.
    - 1 letter, to, Feb 6, 1939; Horckheimer, Max
    - 4 letters, to and from, 1939; Jobling, James W.
    - 1 letter, from, Dec 14, 1939; Kraus, Erik Johannes
    - 11 letters, to and from, 1938-39; LaMer, Victor K.
    - 1 letter, to, April 22, 1939; Liebesny, Herbert
    - 1 letter, to, March 25, 1939; Lucke, Charles E.
    - 2 letters, to and from, Dec. 5, 1938; Lynd, Robert
    - 2 letters, to and from, Dec. 5, 1938; MacIver, Robert M.
    - 3 letters, to and from, 1938; Mark, H.
    - 1 letter, from, Dec 5, 1938; Mitchell, Wesley C.
    - 1 letter, to, Oct. 6, 1939; Montague, W. P.
    - 2 letters, to and from, 1939; Sachs, Bernard
    - 3 letters, to and from, 1938-39; Seligman, Edwin R. A.
    - 3 letters, from, 1939; Simha, Robert
    - 1 letter, to, Oct. 6, 1939; Westerman, W. L.
  - Minutes, May-July 1936 - 1938; 42 items; Emergency Committee... Foreign Scholars, Executive Committee
    - 1 letter, from, Dec. 14, 1937; Appleget, Thomas B.
    - 5 letters, to and from, 1936; Aydelotte, Frank, 1880-1956
    - 1 letter, from, Dec. 7, 1936; Brakeley, George A.
    - 1 letter, to, September 30, 1936; Cohn, Alfred E., (Alfred Einstein), 1879-1957
    - 2 letters, to and from, 1936; Cowdry, E. V., (Edmund Vincent), 1888-1975
    - 2 letters, to and from, 1936, 1937; Drury, Betty
    - 6 letters, to and from, 1936; Duggan, Stephen P.
    - 1 letter, to, Dec. 8, 1937; Farrand, Livingston, 1867-1939
    - 1 letter, from, Dec. 8, 1937; Fields, Harold
    - 4 letters, to and from, 1936; Jayne, Horace H. F.
    - 1 letter, from, September 28, 1936; Lambert, Robert A.
      Includes copy of same
    - 1 letter, from, September 25, 1936; McGregor, J. H.
    - 3 letters, to and from, 1936; Pope, Arthur Upham
    - 1 letter, from, September 21, 1936; Weissenberg, R.
    - 20 letters, to and from, 1936; Whyte, John
  - Emerson, R.A. (Box 12)
  - Emerson, Sterling (Box 12)
  - Encyclopedia Americana (Box 12)
  - Engel, Leonard (Box 12)
    Rogers, Harry S.
  - Engle, Earl T. (Box 12)
  - Ephrussi, Boris, 1932-1941; 25 items (Box 12)
    Biographical and personal data; Educational matters; Population genetics; Research support; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Equality Magazine (Box 12)
  - Evans, Earl A. Jr. (Box 12)
  - Exner, Frank M (Box 12)
    Pendergrass, Eugene P.
  - Fackenthal, Frank D., 1940-1949; 33 items (Box 12)
    Columbia University; Committee activities -- Scientific refugees; Political issues; Recommendations
  - Fermi, Laura (Box 12)
  - Fisher, Ronald Aylmer, 1928-1957; 32 items (Box 12)
    Ford, Edmund Brisco; Human genetics; Mouse genetics; Publication; Wright, Sewall
  - Ford, E.B. (Box 13)
  - Fortuyn, A.B. Droogleever (Box 13)
  - Foster, Morris (Box 13)
  - Friedenwald, Jonas (Box 13)
  - Friedman, Bernard (Box 13)
  - In re: Frolova, S.L. (Box 13)
    British Council
    The Botanical Gazette
  - Fruton, Joseph S. (Box 13)
  - Fulbright Act (Box 13)
  - Furnas, J.C. (Box 13)
  - Gallagher, John W. (Box 13)
  - Garber, E.D. (Box 13)
  - Gates, William H. (Box 13)
  - Genetics Society of America, 1928-1934; 97 items (Box 13)
    Biographical and personal data -- Nominations; Business; Committee activities; Conferences and symposia; Genetics Society of America
  - Genevay, Jacques (Box 13)
  - Gerould, John H., 1919-1955; 14 items (Box 13)
    Biographical and personal data; Graduate study -- Dunn, Leslie Clarence; Recommendations; Teaching
  - Gershenson, S. (Box 13)
    Genetics Society of America
    USSR Society for Cultural Relations with Foreign Countries
  - Geyer-Duszynska, Irene (Box 13)
  - Gilbert, W.M. (Box 13)
  - Giordano, A. (Box 13)
  - Glass, Bentley (Box 13)
  - Gluecksohn-Waelsh, Salome (Box 13)
  - Goldforb (Box 13)
  - Goldschmidt, Elizabeth (Box 13)
  - Goldschmidt, Richard Benedict, 1928-1950; 80 items (Box 13)
    Steinmetzler, Hans
    Picture of Richard Hertwig at his Golden Wedding Ann.
    Displaced German scholars; Drosophila genetics; Evolution; Genetics; History of biology, especially genetics; Mouse genetics; Photographs; Political issues; Russian politics and science; Scientific refugees
  - Goldstein, Lester (Box 13)
  - Goodrich, L. Carrington (Box 13)
  - Gottingen University (Box 13)
  - Gould, John H. (Box 13)
  - Gowen, John W. (Box 13)
  - Graham, Loren (Box 13)
  - Graubard, Marc (Box 13)
  - Gregory, William K. "50 Years in the Dept. of Zoology." (Box 13)
  - Grüneberg, Hans, 1937-1955; 79 items (Box 13)
    Clarke, Hans
    Commission on Exchange
    Conference Board of Associated Research Councils
    Faculty Fellowship Fund
    Green, Earl L.
    Herpers, Richard
    Little, C.C.
    Miller, Harry M. Jr.
    Pomerat, Gerard R.
    U.S. Education Commission in United Kingdom
    Displaced German scholars; Mouse genetics; Research support
  - Gumbel, E.J. (Box 13)
    College of the City of NY
  - in re: Gumbel, Harold (Box 13)
    US Provost Marshal General
  - Hahn, Roger (Box 13)
    Stewart, Ileen E.
  - Haldane, J.B.S. (Box 13)
  - Hammond, John (Box 13)
  - Handler, Philip (Box 13)
    Wallace, Bruce
  - Hankins, J.H. (Box 13)
  - Hanson, Frank Blair (Box 13)
  - Harland, S.C. (Box 14)
  - Harris, Reginald G. (Box 14)
  - Harrison, Ross G. (Box 14)
  - Harron, Robert C. (Box 14)
  - Hartman, Carl G. (Box 14)
  - Harvard College (Box 14)
  - Harvard Talks, etc., 1949 (Box 14)
    Andow, K.
    Edwards, Marvin L.
    Finley, John H., Jr.
    Mangelsdorf, Paul C.
    Pusey, Nathan M.
    Sax, Karl
    Spiess, Eliot B.
    Welsh, J.H.
  - Harvard University - Bussey Inst. (Box 14)
  - Harvey, Clare (Mrs. Leslie) (Box 14)
  - The Harvey Society (Box 14)
  - Hecht, Selig (Box 14)
  - Hematology (Box 14)
  - Herald Tribune (Box 14)
  - Herndon, C. Nash ( American Journal of Human Genetics) (Box 14)
  - Herskowitz, Irwin H. (Box 14)
  - Hertwig, Paula (Box 14)
  - Heston, W.E. (Box 14)
  - Hodgins, Eric (Box 14)
  - Hoecker, Gustavo (Box 14)
  - Hogben, Lancelote (Box 14)
  - Holman, S.P. (Box 14)
  - Holtfreter, Johannes (Box 14)
  - Howard, Alma (Mrs. P. Rolleston) (Box 14)
  - Howson, Roger (Box 14)
  - Hubbard, M.M., Jr. (Box 14)
  - Hughes, Roscoe D. (Box 14)
  - Hull, Fred H. (Box 14)
  - Human Betterment Foundation (Box 14)
    Popenoe
  - Humphrey, Elliot S. (Box 14)
    Fortunate Fields
    Scott, J.W. Robertson
  - Hunt, H.R. (Box 14)
  - Huskins, C. Leonard (Box 14)
  - Hutchison, C. (Box 14)
  - Hutt, F.B. (Box 14)
  - Huxley, Julian, 1930-1961; 36 items (Box 14)
    Conferences and symposia; Drosophila genetics; Genetics -- Gammarus; Poultry genetics; Publication; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
  - Iljin, N.A. (Box 14)
  - Illustrations (Box 14)
  - Iltis, Hugo, 1938-1956; 215 items (Box 14)
    Combs, Morgan L.
    Crampton, Henry E.
    Drury, Elizabeth
    Duval
    Galland, Theodore H.
    Johnson, Edward C.
    Lancefield, Donald E.
    Liebamn, Charles A.
    Lisowski, Eunice
    Ogden, L. Ray
    Pease, Michael
    Shull, George H.
    Spillman, Ramsay
    Walter, Maria
    Biographical and personal data -- Iltis, Hugo; Displaced German scholars; History of biology, especially genetics; History of biology, especially genetics -- Mendel, Gregor; Mendel Museum of Genetics
  - Index to Interviews of Dunn, L.C. by Saul Benison (Box 14)
  - Institute of International Education (Box 14)
    Hopper, Franklin
  - International Congress of Genetics (7th: 1937: Moscow/Edinburgh), 1935-1939; 2 folders (66 items) (Box 25)
    International Congress of Genetics -- Seventh Congress; Political issues; Russian politics and science
  - International Student Service (Box 14)
    Bilheimer, Robert S.
    Bowles, Frank H.
    Cohn, Alfred E.
    Eagleton, Clyde
    Elliott, A. Roland
    Lash, Joseph P.
    Lee, Josephine
    Morley, Loiuse
    Ross, Irwin
    Spivack, Robert G.
  - Introduction to the History of Genetics (Box 14)
  - Istituto Della Enciclopedia Italiana (Box 14)
    Cappelletti, V.
    Ferrabino, Aldo
    Moller, Knud Max
    Montalenti, G.
    Perkins, David
  - Itikawa, Nobukazu (Box 14)
  - Ivanyi, Pavol, 1967-1970; 64 items (Box 15)
    Snell, George
    Walters, Mrs. J.
    Conferences and symposia; Immunogenetics; Mouse genetics; Population genetics; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Ives, Irving M. (Box 15)
  - Jakob, Krivshenko (Box 15)
  - Jenkins, E.H. (Box 15)
  - Jennings, Herbert S. (Box 15)
  - Jensen, Arthur R. (Box 15)
    Alvarez, Walter C.
    Northrup, John H.
    Schockley, W.
    Sporn, Philip
    Stinchcombe, Arthur L.
  - Jessup, Philip C. (Box 15)
  - Johanssen, Wilhelm (Box 15)
    Dictionary of Sci. Biography
  - Johnson, Alvin (Box 15)
    Ephrussi, Boris
  - Johnson, Douglas (Box 15)
  - Johnston, J.B. (Box 15)
  - Jollos, Victor, 1967-1970; 35 items (Box 15)
    Allen, Bennet M.
    Atkinson, Alfred
    Brandt, Karl
    Brink, R.
    Chambers, Robert
    Farmer, Laurence
    Meyer, Karl F.
    Michaelis, Leonore
    Noland, Lowell E.
    Razovsky, Cecilia
    Riesen, E.R.
    Sobotka, Harry
    Displaced German scholars; Russian politics and science
  - Jones, A. Lexington (Box 15)
  - Jones, Donald F. (Box 15)
  - Jones, Lucien Arthur (Box 15)
  - Joravsky, David (Box 15)
  - Journal of Heredity, 1928-1933; 47 items (Box 15)
    Castle, William E.
    Eineneth(?), A.A.
    Levit, S.
    Newman, H.H.
    Snyder, Larry H.
    Tulloss, E.G.
    Publication -- Journal of Heredity; Radiation genetics; Reviews
  - Just, Theodore (Box 15)
  - Kaburaki, Tokio (Box 15)
  - Kaiser, Sam (Box 15)
  - Kamenoff, Ralph (Box 15)
  - Kastenmeier, Robert W. (Box 15)
  - Kaufman, Irving (Box 15)
  - Kaufmann, D.P. (Box 15)
  - Kaunitz, Hans (Box 15)
  - Keeler, Clyde E. (Box 15)
  - Kelner, Albert (Box 15)
  - Kennedy, John F. (Box 15)
  - Kilgore Bill, 1943-1950; 78 items (Box 15)
    National Science Foundation; Political issues -- Kilgore Bill
  - Kilgore and Magnuson Bills, revised (Box 16)
  - King, Helen Dean (Box 16)
  - Kjell, Jeanne Coyne see: Mossige (Box 16)
  - Kohler, Wolfgang (Box 16)
  - Koller, George (Box 16)
  - Kolner, Albert (Box 16)
  - Koltzoff, N.K. (Box 16)
  - Koltzova, Maria and Nick (Box 16)
  - Koopman, Karl (Box 16)
    Parshley, H.M.
    Smith, Emil L.
  - Kopec, Stefan (Box 16)
  - KC6rC6sy, Francis (Box 16)
  - KC6rC6sy, K. (Box 16)
  - Kostoff, Dontcho (Box 16)
  - Kotschnig, Walter M. (Box 16)
  - Krascheninnikow, S. (Box 16)
  - Kreyberg, Leiv (Box 16)
  - Krimbas, Costas (Box 16)
  - Krivshenko, Jakob (Box 16)
    Tolstoy Foundation
    Travelers Aid Society of NY
  - Krizenecky, Jar (Box 16)
  - Krout, John A. (Box 16)
    Hecht, Selig
    Sarton, George
  - Kuang, H.H. (Box 16)
  - Kühn, Alfred (Box 16)
  - Kunkel, B.W. (Box 16)
  - Lack, Harold E. (Box 16)
  - Lamoreux, W.F. (Box 16)
  - Lancefield, D.E. (Box 16)
  - Landauer, Erich (Box 16)
  - Landauer, Naomi (Box 16)
  - Landauer, Walter, 1924-1974; 1,080 items (Box 16)
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Biographical and personal data; Committee activities; David, Paul R.; Displaced German scholars; Embryology, developmental genetics; Ethical issues; History of biology, especially genetics; Immunogenetics; Mouse genetics; Philosophy of science; Poetry and literature; Political issues; Population genetics; Poultry genetics; Scientific refugees; Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1924 April 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1924 July 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1924 September 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1924 September 23] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1926 February 4,7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1926 October 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1926 October 9 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1926 October 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1926 November 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1926 November 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1926 December 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1927] February 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 March 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 March 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [ca.1927?] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 April 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 April 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 April 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1927] April 24 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 May 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 May 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 May 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 June 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1927] June 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 June 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 July 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 July 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 July 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 July 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 August 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 August 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 September 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 October 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1927] October 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 November 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1927 November 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1928 August 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1928 October 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1928 November 9 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1928 December 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1928 Dec. 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1928 December 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1928] No Date 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 January 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 January 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 February 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 Feb. 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 March 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 March 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1929 April 8] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 April 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 April 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 April 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 May 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 May 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 May 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 May 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 May 22 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 June 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 June 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 July 9 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 August 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 Aug. 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 September 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 Sept. 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 Sept. 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 Sept. 12 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 Sept. 24 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 October 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 November 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 Nov. 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 December 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 Dec. 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 Dec. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1929 Dec. 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 January 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 January 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1930 Jan. 27] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 February 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 Feb. 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 Feb. 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1930 March 8] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 Mar. 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1930 April 4] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 Apr. 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 May 5 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1930 May 12] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1930 May 20] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1930 May 21] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 June 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 June 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 July 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 September 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 October 18 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 October 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1930] November 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1930] November 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 December 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1930 December 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1930] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 January 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 February 10 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 Feb. 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 March 2 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 Mar. 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 Mar. 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1931 April 26] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 May 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 May 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 June 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 July 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1931 July 20] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 August 11 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1931] August 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 August 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 September 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1931 October 20] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 November 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 December 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 December 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 December 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 December 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1931 December 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1931 December 30] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1931] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1932 Feb. 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1932 Feb. 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1932 April 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1932 April 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1932 May 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1932 May 13] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1932 June 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1932 Sept. 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1932 Dec. 18] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1932] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1932 Dec.; Jan. 1-16,1933 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 Jan. 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 Feb. 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 March 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 April 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 May 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 June 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 June 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 July 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1933 Aug. 7] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 Aug. 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 Sept. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 Sept. 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 Oct. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 Oct. 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1933] Nov. 9 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 Nov. 14 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1933 Dec. 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1933 Dec. 20] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1933 Dec. 29] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 Jan. 17 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 Feb. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 March 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 April 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 April 9 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 May 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 June 6 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1934] June 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 June 16 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1934 June 21] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 June 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 July 7 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 July 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 Aug. 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 Sept. 15 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 Nov. 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1934 Dec. 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 Jan. 31 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 Feb. 8 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 Feb. 26 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 April 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 April 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 May 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 May 13 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 May 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 June 3 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 June 19 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 June 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 Aug. 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 Sept. 20 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 Sept. 27 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 Oct. 29 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1935 Nov. 1 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, [1935 Nov. 13] (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 Jan. 25 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 Feb. 4 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 Feb. 24 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 Feb. 28 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 April 23 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 April 30 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 May 21 (Box 17-19)
    - to L. C. Dunn, 1936 June 17 (Box 17-19)